Are you maxing out your subscription?
No, not yet? So, start loop engineering
and start cloud routines, codex,
automations, and implement some task
autonomously. And if you want to know
how to set up your loops, watch this
video because we have some tools for
you. And watch, subscribe. Thank you.
>> We show you how to build a loop, to
create your loop, and keep checking a
loop.
>> Matthew Berman, he's a YouTuber, like AI
YouTuber, and he shared his loop library
to like set up automation/routines.
And yeah, cloud and codex. The lazy
loops I I can discover. Discover will
look through your code base and chat
thread to find potential loops. It will
design for you. It's kind of like a
skill creator stuff, but on the loops.
So, if you drop that into your code
base, I'm pretty sure there is some
stuff that you can implement as a loop.
>> Okay, that's cool.
>> Yeah, and his library while you pop a
food AI and can move quickly, but an
open open-ended instruction like keep
improving this
>> is too much room for guessing. A loop
gives the work a clear finish line and a
consistent way to judge progress. That
makes the work easier to trust and
easier to repeat. Yeah, again, like you
need a self a safe end state.
>> Yeah, you need boundaries.
>> So, what's the loop library skill does?
Give you your agent direct access to the
to the IDs in the library. Discover
repeated work in the code base, coding
thread, and all both and turn the
strongest qualified candidates into a
loop. Find the push loop that fits what
you are doing to get done, audit an
existing loop for weak checks, adapt a
useful loops, design a new a new loop
through a short and plain language
conversation, turn the result into a
compact prompt. Okay, install. I want
the list of loops. Discover, find loop
doctor. Okay, audit a loop you passed.
Okay, adapt, tailor useful to your real
tools. I thought it was a list of loops
he was using, which is what I've done,
but uh not it's something Okay, it's
smarter than uh what I thought because
that dynamic, you drop that and then you
get the loops that you need.
>> Yeah, so it actually analyzes your code.
>> Yes. That's cool.
>> Okay, there's something I don't
understand uh because that's the loops.
Yeah, copy loops. The full product
evaluation loop, the 5-minute repository
maintainer, the refund follow-up loop,
get my refund for Oh, okay. Get my
refund for company and charging info,
start the claim. No, okay. LaTeX
document bro, LaTeX, but never use it.
The one post week, one post a week loop,
find a repeatable weekly post format
from approve account through a 6-week
experiment. Oh, people Okay, okay, okay.
So, he used a tool to discover the loops
and then you have a library for people
to post their own loops. Copy the loop,
build sanitized production scale local
data under production like settings,
inventory, every user-facing feature,
role button, root button input model
state, each find documented acceptance
criteria, and finish risk base each case
for each test as a real user logging
every bug with reproduction evidence.
Inventory product product surface meets
its documented acceptance criteria.
Okay, that's cool. I mean, okay, that
makes sense if you have a good user
story board.
>> The question is, I want to run it
because if you don't know and it keeps
on looping and it keeps on making
mistakes, it can be either very
expensive or just mess up everything.
And that's like one of the experiences I
had with Loop I said, just keep on
improving. It had a bug, it looped it,
it had to change something else to fix
the bug, but that created another bug,
and eventually it just kept on looping
on fixing bugs.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you either need good boundaries like
we just said or a very good preparation,
but people who think that the loops are
just something that you add and it
creates the perfect system, I don't
believe that's true.
>> Since the age of AI development, you
need to be really good at product
management. Like you need to really have
good user story and be clear with the
architecture that you have in mind and
like to know where you going because
yes, like the AI can code but the AI
will code crappy if you don't have
a GitHub issues and these and whatever,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> It will just do everything to accomplish
a task that you gave it without
additional subtasks.
>> Yeah. No, exactly.
>> And again, even more if you don't have a
deterministic end state of the loop.
>> Because I watched the video like okay,
no, I I watched the video and then I
drop it in the in the transcript to to
code but for Matthew, he talked about
the loop stuff and he said okay, so I
have a loops that are deterministic but
also AI based where it tell the agents
that until do XYZ until it's acceptable.
>> Yeah, but that's
>> What does it mean?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I I would rather have a loop that
okay, reach 80% coverage run for 2
hours.
>> Yeah. Well, I think that's the same
thing like telling your kid you can
watch TV when you're done cleaning the
house and the cleaning needs to be
acceptable.
>> Yeah.
>> So, they will just vacuum like the whole
that's it and go watch TV.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean yeah, and so the accept the
acceptance criteria will be until I I
say so.
>> Yeah.
>> You can set up the loop and it can do a
lot of work but the preparations need to
be properly done. You need to know
exactly what you want, how you want it,
how secure does it need to be, what
happens if A, what happens if B and you
can still do that discussing it with the
AI but
>> Mhm.
>> you cannot just trust that the loop
makes all the right decisions.
>> That's my Vincent ship sits loops report
where yeah, clean template and prompt
from Codex automation code routines and
recurring agent loops. Copy paste inside
your prompt. Yeah, so you you drop that
to your agent and it will set up the
loops for you. The list of loops that I
have. Code hygiene, content factory
maintenance, which is improve the
project content docs prompt and skill
pipeline with one small high-leverage
maintenance pass. So yeah, also reduce
the size of the scope of the loop. I
want the loop to touch like five 10
files max and not do a full crazy stuff.
So that Yeah, feature implementation.
That's what I was talking about.
Implement exactly one ready ready issue
from the canonical project board. And so
everything is on GitHub. You go you
check the board. You check the pull
request. Boom, walk tree hard pull GPT-5
XI walk tree boom all of that. And you
can drop all of that routines and boom
it's ready to go.
>> That's cool.
>> Yeah, and it's agent first. So yeah,
it's cool. Essential fix recent commit
review. I just like yeah, double-check
all of the commits and yeah, review new
commits on a GitHub repo master since
the last successful review baseline or
the last 24 hours when the baseline
exists. Fix only high-confidence issues.
Love it. And that and for Claude, do I
have anything different? Link example
schedule task board hygiene dry
refactor. Oh yeah, yeah, that's also a
loop that I like. Perform one small dry
refactor in project. So take whatever
you want in the repo, make it better,
dry it up. Boom. And that's it's not
okay, it's a ultra code 4.8 stuff, but
it's works pretty well. Walk tree prune.
So that's what I was saying like once
every day, I think. Yeah, prune merge
local walk tree and branch for project.
Worked only for the repo GitHub
repository. Do not inspect modify
summarize out of scope project. Fetch
and prune remote. Never delete the main
checkout current branch and merge walk
dirty walk trees or branches with push
commit. Only remove walk trees whose
branch are fully merged into masters,
whose PR are merged. And then I
I get like a bite on my computer back
because work through your something
else. React nightly expansion. Yes, I
like this one. So, I have nightly job
where I can increase the end-to-end pass
on the apps I work on and I just
increase the coverage of the end-to-end
and that's automation is doing it too.
>> Okay. So, are you going to loop? Are you
going to loop?
>> loop, yes. On the bigger projects, I'm
going to loop and see.
And yeah, I hope you're going to
>> token max seeing your subscription every
week, man.
>> Yes, just make the max of what you're
paying. If you're paying for for
millions of tokens, don't stop at 1,000.
>> If you're not burning 1 billion token
per day, you're not even coding, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> Michel, thank you so much for your time.
Everyone in the chat, thank you. Bye,
everyone. Bye-bye.
>> Bye.
>> And subscribe. Thank you.